https://www.muncywinds.com/privacy-policy-cookie-restriction-mode

Muncy Winds Music Co
Search:
Search
Cart
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Compare
You have no items to compare.
Home
Woodwind Clarinet Clarinets A ClarinetsBb ClarinetsC ClarinetsD ClarinetsEb ClarinetsAlto ClarinetsBass ClarinetsClarinet Reeds Bb Clarinet ReedsAlto Clarinet ReedsBass Clarinet ReedsContra Bass Clarinet ReedsEb Clarinet ReedsClarinet Reed CasesClarinet Reed Tools & SuppliesClarinet Mouthpieces Alto Clarinet MouthpiecesBass Clarinet MouthpiecesBb Clarinet MouthpiecesContra Bass Clarinet MouthpiecesEb Clarinet MouthpiecesClarinet Mouthpiece Cushions & PatchesClarinet Ligatures & CapsClarinet Barrels Bb Clarinet BarrelsA Clarinet BarrelsEb Clarinet BarrelsClarinet Stands & PegsClarinet StrapsClarinet Cases Eb Clarinet CasesBass Clarinet CasesBb Clarinet CasesA Clarinet CasesClarinet Care & CleaningClarinet AccessoriesSaxophone Saxophones Sopranino SaxophonesSoprano SaxophonesAlto SaxophonesTenor SaxophonesBaritone SaxophonesBass SaxophonesSaxophone Reeds Alto Saxophone ReedsBaritone Saxophone ReedsSoprano Saxophone ReedsTenor Saxophone ReedsSaxophone Reed CasesSaxophone Reed Tools & SuppliesSaxophone Mouthpieces Alto Saxophone MouthpiecesBaritone Saxophone MouthpiecesSoprano Saxophone MouthpiecesTenor Saxophone MouthpiecesSaxophone Mouthpiece Cushions & PatchesSaxophone Ligatures & CapsSaxophone Stands & PegsSaxophone StrapsSaxophone Cases Soprano Saxophone CasesAlto Saxophone CasesTenor Saxophone CasesBaritone Saxophone CasesSaxophone Care & CleaningSaxophone AccessoriesOboe & English Horn Oboes & E. Horns OboesEnglish HornsOboe & E. Horn Reeds Oboe & English Horn ReedsOboe & English Horn Reed CasesOboe & English Horn Reed Tools & SuppliesOboe & E. Horn Stands & PegsOboe & E. Horn StrapsOboe & E. Horn CasesOboe & E. Horn Care & CleaningOboe & E. Horn AccessoriesBassoon Bassoons BassoonsContrabassoonsBassoon Reeds Bassoon ReedsBassoon Reed CasesBassoon Reed Tools & SuppliesBassoon StandsBassoon StrapsBassoon CasesBassoon Care & CleaningFlute & Piccolo Flutes & Piccolos C FlutesAlto FlutesBass FlutesPiccolosFlute & Piccolo Stands & PegsFlute & Piccolo CasesFlute & Piccolo Care & CleaningFlute & Piccolo AccessoriesBrass Trumpet Trumpets Bb TrumpetsC TrumpetsD TrumpetsEb TrumpetsG TrumpetsBass TrumpetsPocket TrumpetsSlide TrumpetsFlugelhornsTrumpet MouthpiecesTrumpet MutesTrumpet Stands & PegsTrumpet CasesTrumpet Care & CleaningTrumpet AccessoriesTrombone Trombones Tenor TrombonesBass TrombonesValve TrombonesTrombone MouthpiecesTrombone MutesTrombone StandsTrombone CasesTrombone Care & CleaningTuba Tubas B TubasC TubasEb TubasF TubasTuba MouthpiecesTuba MutesTuba StandsTuba CasesTuba Care & CleaningFrench Horn French Horns Single French HornsDouble French HornsFrench Horn MouthpiecesFrench Horn MutesFrench Horn StandsFrench Horn CasesFrench Horn Care & CleaningEuphonium Euphoniums EuphoniumsBaritonesEuphonium MouthpiecesEuphonium MutesEuphonium Care & CleaningEuphonium Cases and BagsString Guitar, Mandolin & Banjo StringsString WindersCaposStrapsAudio CablesCare & CleaningAccessories AudioMusic BooksMusic Stands & Accessories Music StandsMusic Stand AccessoriesMetronomes & Tuners MetronomesTunersTuner AccessoriesConducting BatonsMusician ToolsClearance Clarinet DealsAccessories DealsSaxophone DealsBrass DealsFlute and Piccolo DealsAudio CD DealsOboe and Bassoon DealsOn Sale ClarinetsFlutesTop Seller
Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Muncy Winds Privacy and Security Policy
This privacy policy sets out how Muncy Winds uses and protects any information that you give Muncy Winds when you use this website. Muncy Winds is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. Muncy Winds may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
name
contact information including email address
demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
For the exhaustive list of cookies we collect see the List of cookies we collect section.
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping.
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at sales@muncywinds.com
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to PO Box 422
Sugar Grove, NC
28679.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
List of cookies we collect
The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.
COOKIE nameCOOKIE Description
CART
The association with your shopping cart.
CATEGORY_INFO
Stores the category info on the page, that allows to display pages more quickly.
COMPARE
The items that you have in the Compare Products list.
CURRENCY
Your preferred currency
CUSTOMER
An encrypted version of your customer id with the store.
CUSTOMER_AUTH
An indicator if you are currently logged into the store.
CUSTOMER_INFO
An encrypted version of the customer group you belong to.
CUSTOMER_SEGMENT_IDS
Stores the Customer Segment ID
EXTERNAL_NO_CACHE
A flag, which indicates whether caching is disabled or not.
FRONTEND
You sesssion ID on the server.
GUEST-VIEW
Allows guests to edit their orders.
LAST_CATEGORY
The last category you visited.
LAST_PRODUCT
The most recent product you have viewed.
NEWMESSAGE
Indicates whether a new message has been received.
NO_CACHE
Indicates whether it is allowed to use cache.
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART
A link to information about your cart and viewing history if you have asked the site.
POLL
The ID of any polls you have recently voted in.
POLLN
Information on what polls you have voted on.
RECENTLYCOMPARED
The items that you have recently compared.
STF
Information on products you have emailed to friends.
STORE
The store view or language you have selected.
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE
Indicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.
VIEWED_PRODUCT_IDS
The products that you have recently viewed.
WISHLIST
An encrypted list of products added to your Wishlist.
WISHLIST_CNT
The number of items in your Wishlist.
About Muncy Winds Music Co
Muncy Winds Music Was founded in 1987 in Denton, Texas. We specialize in the highest quality instruments and equipment for wind musicians at an affordable price. We appreciate our long time supporters as well as our newest supporters. Please feel free to let us know how we may help you today and in the future.
Learn More
Customer Service
Store Hours
Repair Information
Returns
Order Information
Advanced Search
Sitemap
Mailing Address:
MUNCY WINDS MUSIC CO.
